[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1943, Butterfly McQueen appeared in this Vincent Minelli/ Busby Berkly directed movie with an African- American cast including Ethel Waters, Louis Armstrong, and Eddie Rochester Anderson.", "correct_answer": "Cabin in the Sky", "incorrect_answers": ["Duel in the Sun", "Harlem Revue of 1943", "Affectionately Yours"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these is not a species of zebra?", "correct_answer": "Savanna Zebra", "incorrect_answers": ["Cape Mountain Zebra", "Grevys Zebra", "Plains Zebra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these vegetables is not a type of broccoli?", "correct_answer": "Chinese broccoli", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Romanesco broccoli", "Purple cauliflower"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which country has the highest population density according to 2009 estimates?", "correct_answer": "Peoples Republic of China", "incorrect_answers": ["Indonesia", "India", "United States"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Philippine blood stew is made by using the heart and blood of a pig.", "correct_answer": "Diniguan", "incorrect_answers": ["Ngapi-jaw", "Blazing curry", "Durian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This street parade, seen in the 1965 film, Thunderball, helps Bond elude his pursuers.", "correct_answer": "Junkanoo", "incorrect_answers": ["Holiputra", "Agawinti", "Milabudu"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On the movie The Break-Up, Brooke wanted Gary to bring home 13 lemons.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The ileum is located in this part of the body.", "correct_answer": "Small Intestine", "incorrect_answers": ["Spinal cord", "Brain", "Large intestine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the three classical types of columns has its capital ornately decorated to look like acanthus leaves?", "correct_answer": "Corinthian", "incorrect_answers": ["Ionic", "Tonic", "Doric"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "We\u2019ve seen these animals as friendly and approachable but the truth is that they\u2019re unpredictable. What is the average number of fatalities a year elephants cause?", "correct_answer": "300-500", "incorrect_answers": ["150-200", "20-40", "1000-1500"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Turtles have poor vision and cannot see in color.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1987 movie received the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Picture?", "correct_answer": "Leonard Part 6", "incorrect_answers": ["Whos That Girl", "Jaws: The Revenge", "Tough Guys Dont Dance"]}]